Guide to the Alan Farley Collection ARS.0067
Archive of Recorded Sound
- 2008 Book Talk Episodes, 2007-2008; 28 compact discs (Audio 12)
  1 compact disc with a Microsoft Excel document with an index of 2007 digital audio tapes [transferred from Box 11]
  B0801; Diffee, Matthew; The Rejection Collection, Vol. 2; 11/19/2007; 1/6/2008 (:30)
  B0802; Hayes, Bill; The Anatomist; 1/11/2008; 1/13/2008 (:30)
  B0803; Auster, Paul; Travels in the Scriptorium; 1/15/2008; 1/20/2008 (:30)
  B0804; Leleux, Robert; The Memoirs of a Beautiful Boy; 1/23/2008; 1/27/2008 (:30)
  B0805; Cannell, Stephen; Three Shirt Deal; 1/25/2008; 2/3/2008 (:30)
  B0806; Kennedy, Randall; Sellout: The Politics of Betrayal; 1/15/2008; 2/10/2008 (:30)
  B0807; Ross, Janice; The San Francisco Ballet at 75; 1/31/2008; 2/17/2008 (:30)
  B0808; Flanders, Laua; Blue Grit; 2/13/2008; 2/24/2008 (:30)
  B0809; Banks, Russell; The Reserve; 2/14/2008; 3/2/2008 (:30)
  B0810; Carey, Peter; His Illegal Self; 2/26/2008; 3/9/2008 (:30)
  B0811; Lutz, Lisa; Curse of the Spellmans; 3/11/2008; 3/16/2008 (:30)
  B0812; Heim, Scott; We Disappear; 3/18/2008; 3/23/2008 (:30)
  B0813; Rarick, Ethan; Desperate Journey; 3/26/2008; 3/30/2008 (:30)
  B0814; Ariely, Dan; Predictably Irrational; 3/4/2008; 4/6/2008 (:33)
  B0814; Wollenberg, Charles; Berkeley: A City in History; 3/24/2008; 4/6/2008 (:14)
  B0815; Ross, Alex; The Rest Is Noise: Listening to the 20th Century; 10/19/2007; 4/13/2008 (:44)
  B0816; Kaku, Michio; Physics of the Impossible; 3/28/2008; 4/20/2008 (:30)
  B0817; Black, Cara; Murder in the Rue de Paradis; 4/22/2008; 4/27/2008 (:30)
  B0818; Burton, Robert; On Being Certain; 5/2/2008; 5/4/2008 (:30)
  B0819; Coppola, Eleanor; Notes on a Life; 5/7/2008; 5/11/2008 (:30)
  B0820; Winchester, Simon; The Man Who Loved China; 5/12/2008; 5/18/2008 (:30)
  B0821; Perlstein, Rick; Nixonland; 5/14/2008; 5/25/2008 (:30)
  B0822; Greer, Andrew Sean; The Story of a Marriage; 5/15/2008; 6/1/2008 (:30)
  B0823; Eng, Tan Twan; The Gift of Rain; 5/16/2008; 6/8/2008 (:30)
  B0824; George, Elizabeth; Careless in Red; 5/19/2008; 6/15/2008 (:30)
  B0825; Zakaria, Fareed; The Post American World; 5/27/2008; 6/22/2008 (:30)
  B0826; Patel, Raj; Stuffed and Starved; 6/4/2008; 6/29/2008 (:30)
  B0827; Martini, Steve; Shadow of Power; 5/30/2008; 7/6/2008 (:30)
  B0828; Price, David; The Pixar Touch; 6/10/2008; 7/13/2008 (:30)
  B0829; Lakoff, George; The Political Mind; 7/24/2008; 7/20/2008 (:30)
  B0830; Deaver, Jeffrey; The Broken Window; 6/18/2008; 7/27/2008 (:30)
  B0831; Sedaris, David; When You Are Engulfed in Flames; 6/26/2008; 8/3/2008 (:30)
  B0832; Hafner, Katie; A Love Affair on Three Legs; 7/2/2008; 8/10/2008 (:30)
  B0833; Ehrenreich, Barbara; This Land Is Their Land; 7/14/2008; 8/17/2008 (:30)
  B0834; Gold, Herb; Still Alive: A Temporary Condition; 7/21/2008; 8/31/2008 (:30)
  B0835; Reed, Ishmael; Mixing It Up: Taking on the Media Bullies and Other Reflections; 7/30/2008; 8/31/2008 (:30)
  B0836; English, T. J.; Havana Nocturne; 7/29/2008; 9/7/2008 (:30)
  B0837; Kureishi, Hanif; Something to Tell You; 9/12/2008; 9/14/2008 (:30)
  B0838; Bernstein, David; S. F. Tape Music Center; 8/29/2008; 9/21/2008 (:60)
  B0839; Lyall, Sarah; The Anglo Files: A Field Guide to the British; 9/17/2008; 9/28/2008 (:30)
  B0840; Conant, Jennet; The Irregulars: Roald Dahl and the British Spy Ring in Wartime Washington; 9/17/2008; 10/5/2008 (:30)
  B0841; Aguilar, Rose; Red Highways; 10/9/2008; 10/12/2008 (:30)
  B0842; Maguire, Gregory; A Lion Among Men: Volume Three of the Wicked Years; 10/14/2008; 10/19/2008 (:30)
  B0843; Barry, Dave; Science Fair; 10/20/2008; 10/26/2008 (:30)
  B0844; Sterry, David; Master of Ceremonies; 10/22/2008; 11/2/2008 (:30)
  B0845; Roach, Mary; Bonk: The Curious Coupling of Science and Sex; 10/30/2008; 11/9/2008 (:30)
  B0846; Bell, Janis; Clean, Well-Lighted Sentences; 11/10/2008; 11/16/2008 (:30)
  B0847; Blount, Jr, Roy; Alphabet Juice; 11/10/2008; 11/23/2008 (:30)
  B0848; Kanfer, Stefan; Somebody: The Reckless Life and Remarkable Career of Marlon Brando; 11/20/2008; 12/7/2008 (:30)
  B0849; Thomson, David; Have You Seen?; 12/1/2008; 12/14/2008 (:30)
  B0850; Trillin, Calvin; Deciding the Next Decider; 12/5/2008; 12/28/2008 (:30)
- 2009 Book Talk Episodes, 2008-2009; 25 compact discs (Audio 13)
  Episode Number; Last Name, First Name; Profession; Book Title; Record Date; Air Date (Length:Minutes): Subject Matter
  B0901; James, P. D.; Author; The Private Patient; 12/12/2008; 1/4/2009 (:30): She talks about her latest Adam Dalgliesh novel, and at age 88, it might be the last one
  B0902; Cannell, Stephen J.; Writer, Producer; On the Grind; 1/9/2009; 1/11/2009 (:30): He talks about his new Shane Scully novel, and about television and his dyslexia and more
  B0903; Malmont, Paul; Author; Jack London in Paradise; 1/13/2009; 1/18/2009 (:30): He talks about his novel about Jack London's last year, spent in Hawaii
  B0904; Fishburne, Rodes; Author; Going to See the Elephant; 1/14/2009; 2/1/2009 (:30): He talks about his first novel, set in contemporary San Francisco
  B0905; Gopnik, Adam; Writer; Angels and Ages; 1/27/2009; 2/8/2009 (:30): He talks about his book about Abraham Lincoln and Charles Darwin, who were born on the same day in 1809
  B0906; Harris, E. Lynn; Author; Basketball Jones; 2/13/2009; 2/15/2009 (:30): He talks about his latest novel about a gay man in ove with an NBA player; and about his career
  B0907; Thomson, David; Writer; Try to Tell the Story; 2/13/2009; 2/22/2009 (:30): His memoir of growing up in England, to age 18
  B0908; Fairstein, Linda; Author; Lethal Legacy; 2/17/2009; 3/1/2009 (:30): She talks about her latest Alexandra Cooper mystery, set in and around the New York Public Library
  B0909; Ricks, Thomas; Author, Journalist; Gamble; 2/23/2009; 3/8/2009 (:30): He talks about his nbook about General Petreus and the war in Iraq
  B0910; Winspear, Jacquelline; Author; Among the Mad; 2/23/2009; 3/15/2009 (:30): She talks about her latest Masie Dobbs mystery
  B0911; Gores, Joe; Writer; Spade and Archer; 3/18/2009; 3/22/2009 (:30): He talks about writing the prequel to "The Maltese Falcon" and his former career as a private detective
  B0912; Robinson, Peter; Author; All the Colors of Darkness; 2/25/2009; 3/29/2009 (:30): He talks about his latest Inspector Alan Banks novel
  B0913; Davis, Tom; Writer; 39 Years of Short-Term Memory Loss; 3/18/2009; 4/5/2009 (:30): He talks about his years as a writer for Saturday Night Live and more
  B0914; Mosley, Walter; Author; The Long Fall; 4/1/2009; 4/12/2009 (:30): He talks about the first novel in his new series about his New York detective Leonid McGill
  B0915; George, Nelson; Author; City Kid; 4/15/2009; 4/19/2009 (:30): He talks about his memoir of growing up in Brooklyn, and his subsequent success as a writer and fillmaker
  B0916; Day, Barry; The Letters of Noel Coward; Writer; 4/16/2009; 4/26/2009 (:30): He talks about the book of letters, and this other work relating to Noel Coward
  B0917; Glantz, Aaron; Journalist; The War Comes Home; 5/1/2009; 5/3/2009 (:30): He talks about his book about the govenrment's treatment of Iraq and Afghanistan war veterans
  B0918; Ginoli, Jon; Musician; Deflowered: My Life in Pansy Division; 5/4/2009; 5/10/2009 (:30): He talks about founding the first gay punk-pop band 20 years ago, and its progress
  B0919; Miller, Logan & Noah; Filmmaker; You're In or In the Way; 5/5/2009; 5/17/2009 (:30): The twin brothers talk about their book about their quest to make a movie about their late father
  B0920; Bogosian, Eric; Author, Actor; Perforated Heart; 5/12/2009; 5/24/2009 (:30): He talks about his new novel, his early career, and his continuing role on "Law & Order: Criminal Intent" on TV
  B0921; Whitehead, Colson; Author; Sag Harbor; 5/19/2009; 5/31/2009 (:30): He talks about the sutobiographical nature of his new novel
  B0922; Nunberg, Geoffrey; Linguist; The Years of Talking Dangerously; 5/20/2009; 6/7/2009 (:30): He talks about his compliation of pieces from Fresh Air, NY Times, LA Times, etc.
  B0923; Dyson, Michael Eric; Professor, Author; Can You Hear Me Now? 5/27/2009; 6/14/2009 (:30): He talks about the collection of his thoughts over the past twenty years
  B0924; Lewis, Michael; Author; Home Game; 6/9/2009; 6/21/2009 (:30): He talks about his book about fatherhood and his three children
  B0925; de Botton, Alain; Author; The Pleasures and Sorrows of Work; 6/10/2009; 6/28/2009 (:30): He talks about why and how he wrote the book
  B0926; Child, Lee; Author; Gone Tomorrow; 6/6/2009; 7/5/2009 (:30): He talks about his latest Jack Reacher thriller, and the origin and evolution of the series
  B0927; Lescroart, John; Author; A Plague of Secrets; 7/2/2009; 7/12/2009 (:30): He talks about his latest San Francisco-based legal thriller
  B0928; Farrell, Mike; Actor; Of Mule and Man; 6/25/2009; 7/19/2009 (:30) He talks about his journal of his 9000 mile trip around the country on the book tour for the paperback edition of "Call Me Mike"
  B0929; Sethi, Ali; Author; The Wish Maker; 6/22/2009; 7/26/2009 (:30): He talks about ihis first novel, and his study at Harvard and in his native Pakistan
  B0930; Gavin, James; Author; Stormy Weather: The Life of Lena Horne; 7/15/2009; 8/2/2009 (:30): He talks about why and how he wrote this biography
  B0931; Krassner, Paul; Satirist; In Praise Of Indecency; 7/14/2009; 8/9/2009 (:30): He talks about his book and the state of comedy and politics today
  B0932; Laird, Nick; Author; Glover's Mistake; 7/22/2009; 8/16/2009 (:30): He talks about his new novel, writing poetry and making book tours
  B0933; Ellis, David; Author, Lawyer; The Hidden Man. Pledge Special; 9/10/2009; 9/13/2009 (:60): He talks about his latest mystery, and his legal career, which included leading the impeachment of Illinois Governor Rod Blagojevich.Dianne Keogh joins Alan for some book recommendations
  B0934; Baker, Nicholson; Author; The Anthologist; 9/17/2009; 9/20/2009 (:30): He talks about his new novel, and about studying music at Eastman, and how he started writing after deciding he wasn't making it in music
  B0935; Bartlett, Allison Hoover; Author; The Man Who Loved Books Too Much; 9/21/2009; 9/27/2009 (:30): She tells us how and why she wrote about book thief John Gilkey
  B0936; Winn, Steven; Journalist; Come Back, Como; 9/24/2009; 10/4/2009 (:30): He tells why he wrote this book about the family's difficult dog, and about how he has after having left the Chronicle after 28 years
  B0937; Hornby, Nick; Author; Juliet, Naked; 10/8/2009; 10/11/2009 (:30) He talks about his new novel and the new film he has written, "An Education"
  B0938; Cheuse, Alan; Author; A Trance Before Breakfast; 10/16/2009; 10/18/2009 (:30): He talks about his travel book, and his reviews for NPR
  B0939; Colfer, Eoin; Author; And Another Thing...; 10/8/2009; 11/1/2009 (:30): He talks about continuing the Hitchhiker's Guide to the GAlaxy series, and his own series, Artemis Fowl
  B0940; Nachman, Gerald; Author; Right Here on Our Stage Tonight: Ed Sullivan's America; 11/3/2009; 11/8/2009 (:30): He talks about how and why he wrote the book
  B0941; Hodgman, John; Author; The Areas of My Expertise; 2/10/2006; 11/15/2009 (:30): With musician Jonathan Coulton. Rebroadcast B0942; Hertzberg, Rick; Journalist; Obamanos!; 11/18/2009; 11/22/2009 (:30): The birth of a new political era
  B0943; West, Cornel; Professor; Brother West: Living and Loving Out Loud - A Memoir; 11/20/2009; 11/29/2009 (:30): He talks about his memoir and his life
  B0944; Sam, Canyon; Author, Activist; Sky Train; 12/1/2009; 12/6/2009 (:30): She talks about her visits to Tibet and how she became an activist
  B0945; Thomson, David; Author; The Moment of Psycho; 12/2/2009; 12/13/2009 (:30): He talks about his latest book, about Alfred Hitchcock and "Psycho"
  B0946; Penzler, Otto; Bookstore Owner, Anthologist; The Lineup; 12/3/2009; 12/20/2009 (:30): He talks about his book, which collects crime fiction writers' description about the creation of their main characters. His interview is 11 min, then David Latulippe, Dianne Keogh and Peter Robinson read excerpts from Ian Rankin, Lee Child and Colin Dexter
  B0947; Linde, Paul; Psychiatrist, Author; Danger to Self: On the Front Line with an ER Psychiatrist; 12/17/2009; 12/27/2009 (:30): He talks about his new book, and working in the ER of S. F. General Hospital